Indiana University President's Office records, 1963-1990 C459
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative records, 1963-1990; undated (Box 1)
  - Keenan Report (Box 167)
    - 1973, (2 folders) (Box 167)
    - 1974 (Box 167)
    - July 1973, (3 folders) (Box 167)
  - W.K. Kellog Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 167)
  - Kent State, 1971-1973 (Box 167)
  - King, Claudia, 1979 (Box 167)
  - Kirkwood gates, 1976 (Box 167)
  - Kl, 1971-1987 (Box 167)
  - Klinge, Paul E., 1971-1978 (Box 167)
  - Knight, Robert M. (Box 167)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 167)
    - Press kit, 1979 (Box 167)
    - News Conference, 1979; (2 folders) (Box 167)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 167)
    - Fire Knight, 1979 (Box 167)
    - Keep Knight, 1979 (Box 167)
    - Knight and Guest, 1981 (Box 167)
    - 1976-1982 (Box 167)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 167)
    - 1983 (Box 167)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 167)
    - 1985 (Box 167)
    - Letters Concerning Knight, 1985; (2 folders) (Box 167)
    - 1986 (Box 167)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 167)
    - 1987 (Box 167)
  - Ko, 1971-1987 (Box 167)
  - Kokomo (City of) (Box 167)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 167)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 167)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 167)
  - Kuwait (Box 167)
    - 1976 (Box 167)
    - January, 1976 (Box 167)
  - L (Box 167)
    - 1971-1983 (Box 168)
    - 1983 (Box 168)
    - 1984 (Box 168)
    - 1985 (Box 168)
    - 1986 (Box 168)
    - 1987 (Box 168)
  - Lak, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lan, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lang, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lar, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Las, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Law, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Le, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lee, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Leh, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Len, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lev, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lew, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Li, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lin, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lio, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lit, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lon, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lot, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Lun, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Ly, 1971-1987 (Box 168)
  - Labor Education (Box 168)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 168)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 168)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 168)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 168)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 168)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 168)
  - Labor Education and Research Center, 1973-1974 (Box 168)
  - Labor Studies (Division of) (Box 168)
    - 1983 (Box 168)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 168)
    - 1985 (Box 168)
    - 1986 (Box 168)
  - Lama Temple (Box 168)
    - 1974-1986 (Box 168)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 168)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 168)
  - Landini, Richard G - Inauguration of, 1975 (Box 168)
  - Latin American Studies (Box 168)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 168)
    - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 168)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 168)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 168)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 168)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 168)
  - Latino Affairs (Box 168)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 169)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 169)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 169)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 169)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 169)
    - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 169)
    - 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 169)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 169)
    - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 169)
    - 1980 (Box 169)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 169)
    - 1981 (Box 169)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 169)
    - 1984 (Box 169)
    - 1985 (Box 169)
  - Law Enforcement Education Program, 1971-1974 (Box 169)
  - Law School (Box 169)
    - Bloomington (Box 169)
      - General, 1970-1971 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1971-1972 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 169)
      - General, 1972-1973 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1972-1973 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1972 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1973-1974 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1974-1975 (Box 169)
      - General, 1975 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1975-1976 (Box 169)
      - Merger Controversy, 1975-1976 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1976-1977 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1977-1978 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 169)
      - Board of Visitors, 1978-1979 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 169)
      - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 169)
      - Bloomington and Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 169)
      - General, 1981-1982 (Box 170)
      - Board of Visitors, 1982 (Box 170)
      - Expansion, 1982 (Box 170)
        - Plager Letters/Maps (Box 170)
          (Includes one plat drawing not included in scans due to poor quality. Contact Archives to view.)
        - Support letters, newsclippings, other letters (Box 170)
        - General (Box 170)
      - General, 1983 (Box 170)
      - General, 1983-1984 (Box 170)
      - Evaluation, 1983-1984 (Box 170)
      - General, 1985 (Box 170)
      - Dedication of Building and Renovations, September 1986 (Box 170)
      - Board of Visitors, 1986; (2 folders) (Box 170)
      - General, 1986-1987 (Box 170)
      - Board of Visitors, 1987 (Box 170)
    - Indianapolis (Box 170)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 170)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 170)
      - Committee on Goals and Objectives, 1971-1972 (Box 170)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 170)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 170)
      - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 170)
      - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 170)
      - Board of Visitors, 1974-1976 (Box 170)
      - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 170)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 170)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 170)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 170)
      - Board of Visitors, 1977-1980 (Box 170)
      - Board of Visitors, 1986 (Box 170)
      - Board of Visitors, 1987 (Box 170)
  - Learning Resources (Box 170)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 170)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 170)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 170)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 170)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 170)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 170)
    - 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 170)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 170)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 170)
  - Legionnaire's Disease, 1978 (Box 170)
  - Lewin, Arnold, 1976 (Box 170)
  - Libraries (Box 170)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 171)
    - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 171)
    - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 171)
    - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 171)
    - 1975-1976, (3 folders) (Box 171)
    - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 171)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 171)
    - 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 171)
    - 1979 (Box 171)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 171)
    - 1980 (Box 171)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 171)
    - 1979-1983 (Box 171)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 171)
    - 1983 (Box 172)
    - 1984 (Box 172)
    - 1985 (Box 172)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 172)
  - Library School (Box 172)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 172)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 172)
    - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - Review, 1973-1976 (Box 172)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 172)
    - 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 172)
    - 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 172)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 172)
    - 1987 (Box 172)
  - Liebenow, J. Gus (Box 172)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 172)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 172)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 172)
  - Eli Lilly and Company (Box 172)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 172)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 172)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 172)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 172)
  - Lilly Endowment (Box 172)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 172)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 172)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 172)
    - 1974 (Box 172)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 172)
    - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 172)
    - 1977 (Box 172)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 172)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 172)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 172)
    - 1980 (Box 172)
    - 1981 (Box 172)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 172)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 172)
    - 1983 (Box 172)
    - 1984 (Box 172)
    - 1985, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 172)
  - Lilly Library (Box 172)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 172)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 172)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 172)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 172)
    - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 172)
    - 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 172)
    - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - 1980 (Box 172)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 172)
    - 1981 (Box 172)
    - 1983 (Box 172)
    - 1984 (Box 172)
    - 1985 (Box 172)
  - Lincoln Hotel, 1986 (Box 173)
  - Little 500 (Box 173)
    - 1978 (Box 173)
    - 1985 (Box 173)
  - Living Learning Center (MRC) (Box 173)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 173)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 173)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 173)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 173)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 173)
    - 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 173)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 173)
    - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 173)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 173)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 173)
  - Interim Loans, 1970-1974 (Box 173)
  - Lo, 1971-1987 (Box 173)
  - Lockfield Gardens, 1980-1981 (Box 173)
  - Long, Preston, and Kinnaird, 1972 (Box 173)
  - Long Range Planning (Box 173)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 173)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 173)
    - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 173)
    - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 173)
    - 1974-1984, (2 folders) (Box 174)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 174)
    - 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 174)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 174)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 174)
  - Louden House, 1977 (Box 174)
  - Lu, 1971-1987 (Box 174)
  - Lundquist, Eldon, 1976-1977 (Box 174)
  - M (Box 174)
    - 1971-1982 (Box 174)
    - 1983 (Box 174)
    - 1984 (Box 174)
    - 1985 (Box 174)
    - 1986 (Box 174)
    - 1987 (Box 174)
  - Mack, 1971-1987 (Box 174)
  - Mad, 1971-1987 (Box 174)
  - Mah, 1971-1987 (Box 174)
  - Mal, 1971-1987 (Box 174)
  - Man, 1971-1987 (Box 174)
  - Mar, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mark, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mart, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mas, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mat, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Matt, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - May, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mc, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - McA, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - McC, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - McD, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - McE, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - McG, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - McI, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - McL, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - McN, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mei, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mer, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mes, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mey, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mi, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mid, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mil, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mill, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mit, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mo, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mob, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Moh, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mon, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Moo, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mor, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Morr, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mos, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mul, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Mur, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Murr, 1971-1987 (Box 175)
  - Madrigal Dinners (Box 175)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 175)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 175)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 175)
  - Mail Service (Box 175)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 175)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 175)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 175)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 175)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 175)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 175)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 175)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 175)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 175)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 175)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 175)
  - Malaysia, 1985 (Box 175)
  - Manpower Program, 1975-1981 (Box 175)
  - Management Information System (Box 175)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 175)
    - Central System Task Force, 1972 (Box 175)
    - Requirements Task Force, 1972 (Box 175)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 176)
    - Steering Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 176)
    - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 176)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 176)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 176)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 176)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 176)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 176)
  - Marah, Momorie, 1978 (Box 176)
  - Management Task Force (Box 176)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 176)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 176)
    - 1973 (Box 176)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 176)
  - Marr, Robert M. Jr., 1969 (Box 176)
  - University of Maryland (Box 176)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 176)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 176)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 176)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 176)
  - University of Massachusetts (Box 176)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 176)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 176)
  - Maternity Leave, 1971-1972 (Box 176)
  - Mathematics Department (Box 176)
    - 1971 (Box 176)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 176)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 176)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 176)
  - Mathers Museum (Box 176)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 176)
    - 1983 (Box 176)
    - 1985 (Box 176)
  - Maxi Duplicating Center, 1974-1980 (Box 176)
  - Mazza, Patricia, 1977-1979 (Box 176)
  - McCalla School, 1974-1975 (Box 176)
  - McKinney, Frank E. Jr., 1974-1978 (Box 176)
  - Me, 1971-1987 (Box 176)
  - Meadowood Retirement Community (Box 176)
    - 1980-1983 (Box 176)
    - 1983 (Box 176)
    - 1984 (Box 176)
  - Medical Sciences Addition (Myers Hall), 1972 (Box 176)
  - Medical Sciences Program, 1970-1975 (Box 176)
  - Menke, Robert H., 1971-1973 (Box 177)
  - Merchants National Bank and Trust Company (Box 177)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 177)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 177)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 177)
  - Merrit, Lynne, 1971-1978 (Box 177)
  - Meyerwitz, William, 1978 (Box 177)
  - Michigan State University (Box 177)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 177)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 177)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 177)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 177)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 177)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 177)
    - 1984 (Box 177)
  - University of Michigan (Box 177)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 177)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 177)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 177)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 177)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 177)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 177)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 177)
    - 1985 (Box 177)
  - Midwestern University Alliance (Box 177)
    - 1983 (Box 177)
    - 1985 (Box 177)
    - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 177)
    - 1987 (Box 177)
  - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities (MUCIA) (Box 177)
    - 1971, (3 folders) (Box 177)
    - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 177)
    - 1972 (Box 177)
    - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 178)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 178)
    - 1974 (Box 178)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 178)
    - Retreat, September 1975 (Box 179)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 179)
    - Retreat, September 1976 (Box 179)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 179)
    - Ford Foundation Meeting, August (Box 179)
    - Retreat, September 1977 (Box 179)
    - 1977 (Box 179)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 179)
    - Board Meeting, May 1978 (Box 179)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 179)
    - Board Meeting, October 1979; (2 folders) (Box 179)
    - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 179)
    - 1980 (Box 179)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 179)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 179)
    - Board Meeting, September 1982 (Box 179)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 180)
    - Wingspread Conference, 1983 (Box 180)
    - 1983 (Box 180)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 180)
    - 1984 (Box 180)
    - 1985 (Box 180)
    - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 180)
    - Retreat, September 1986 (Box 180)
    - 1987, (2 folders) (Box 180)
  - Midwest Universities Energy Consortium (Box 180)
    - 1982 (Box 180)
    - 1983 (Box 180)
    - 1987 (Box 180)
  - Milliken, 1984 (Box 180)
  - Military, 1982-1986 (Box 180)
  - Mini University (Box 180)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 180)
    - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 180)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 180)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 180)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 180)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 180)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 180)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 180)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 180)
    - 1980 (Box 180)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 180)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 180)
  - Mining and Mineral Resources Research Institute (Box 180)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 181)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 181)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 181)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 181)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 181)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 181)
  - Minorities (Box 181)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 181)
  - University of Minnesota (Box 181)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 181)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 181)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 181)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 181)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 181)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 1978 (Box 181)
  - Miscellaneous Requests for Information (Box 181)
    - 1977 (Box 181)
    - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 181)
    - 1985 (Box 181)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 181)
  - Mission Statement (Box 181)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 181)
    - 1987 (Box 181)
  - Momorie, Marah, 1979 (Box 181)
  - Monroe County (Box 181)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 181)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 181)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 181)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 181)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 181)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 181)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 181)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 181)
  - Monroe County Community School Corporation, 1982-1983 (Box 181)
  - Moore, John Duane, 1971-1972 (Box 181)
  - Moore, Willma, 1980 (Box 181)
  - Mortar Board, 1973-1974 (Box 181)
  - Mu, 1971-1987 (Box 181)
  - Muhler, Joseph C. (Box 181)
    - 1979 (Box 181)
    - 1980 (Box 181)
    - 1981 (Box 181)
    - 1983 (Box 181)
    - 1984 (Box 181)
    - 1985 (Box 181)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 181)
  - Multi-Campus Public University Systems, 1979-1981 (Box 181)
  - Multi-Campus University Executives at University of Maryland, 1980 (Box 181)
  - Murray, Rosemary - Vice Chancellor, Cambridge University, 1976-1977 (Box 181)
  - Indiana University Museum (Box 181)
    - General (Box 181)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 181)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 181)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 181)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 181)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 181)
    - Annual Report (Box 181)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 181)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 181)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 181)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 181)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 181)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 181)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 181)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 181)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 182)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 182)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 182)
  - School of Music (Box 182)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 182)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 182)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 182)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 182)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 182)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 182)
    - 1977 (Box 182)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 182)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 182)
    - Music Building Dedication, October 1979 (Box 182)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 182)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 182)
    - Invitation Lists to Metropolitan, 1981 (Box 182)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 182)
    - Passion Play – Carmina Burana, 1982-1983; (2 folders) (Box 182)
    - 1983 (Box 182)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 182)
    - 1984 (Box 182)
    - 1985 (Box 182)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 182)
    - 1987 (Box 182)
    - Annual Report (Box 182)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 182)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 182)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 182)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 182)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 182)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 182)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 182)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 182)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 182)
  - Musical Arts Center (Box 182)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 182)
    - Giselle Performance, 1972 (Box 182)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 182)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 182)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 182)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 182)
  - N (Box 182)
    - 1971-1982 (Box 182)
    - 1983 (Box 182)
    - 1984 (Box 182)
    - 1985 (Box 182)
    - 1986 (Box 182)
    - 1987 (Box 182)
  - Nat, 1971-1987 (Box 182)
  - Ne, 1971-1987 (Box 182)
  - Nel, 1971-1987 (Box 183)
  - Nem, 1971-1987 (Box 183)
  - New, 1971-1987 (Box 183)
  - Ni, 1971-1987 (Box 183)
  - No, 1971-1987 (Box 183)
  - Nor, 1971-1987 (Box 183)
  - Not, 1971-1987 (Box 183)
  - Narcotics (Box 183)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 183)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 183)
  - Natatorium (Box 183)
    - 1980 (Box 183)
    - 1982 (Box 183)
    - 1983 (Box 183)
    - 1984 (Box 183)
  - National A-Z (Box 183)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 183)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 183)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 183)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 183)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 183)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 183)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 183)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 183)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 183)
    - 1981 (Box 183)
    - 1982 (Box 183)
    - 1983 (Box 183)
  - National Academy of Public Administration (Box 183)
    - 1979 (Box 183)
    - 1986 (Box 183)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 183)
    - General (Box 183)
      - 1971-1976 (Box 183)
      - 1979 (Box 183)
      - 1986 (Box 183)
    - National Research Council, 1971-1972 (Box 183)
  - National Advisory Board on International Education Programs (Box 183)
    - 1985 (Box 183)
    - 1986, (3 folders) (Box 183)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 183)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 184)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 184)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 184)
  - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems (NCHEMS), 1979-1980 (Box 184)
  - National Collegiate Athletics Association (NCAA), 1983 (Box 184)
  - National Commission for Cooperative Education, 1979-1981 (Box 184)
  - National Council of Independent Colleges and Universities (Box 184)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 184)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 184)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 184)
  - National Educational Television, 1972 (Box 184)
  - National Educational Television Film Service (Box 184)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 184)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 184)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 184)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 184)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 184)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 184)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 184)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 184)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 184)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 184)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 184)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 184)
  - National Institute for Campus Ministry (Box 184)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 184)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, September 1975 (Box 184)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 184)
    - 1976, (3 folders) (Box 184)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 184)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 184)
    - 1978 (Box 184)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 184)
  - National Institute of Development Administration (Box 184)
    - General, 1977-1987 (Box 184)
    - Visit to Thailand, 30th Anniversary Celebration, 1985 (Box 184)
  - National Institute for Fitness and Sport (Box 184)
    - 1985 (Box 184)
    - Cornerstone Laying, 1986; (2 folders) (Box 184)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 184)
  - National Instructional Television Center (Box 184)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 184)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 184)
  - National Laboratory for Higher Education, 1971-1972 (Box 184)
  - National Office for Black Catholics, 1982 (Box 185)
  - National Research Council (Box 185)
    - 1986 (Box 185)
    - 1987 (Box 185)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 185)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 185)
    - University Science Development Program, Grant Request, February 1972 (Box 185)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 185)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 185)
    - Panel, 1974 (Box 185)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 185)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 185)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 185)
    - Nominations, 1977-1978 (Box 185)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 185)
    - 1978 (Box 185)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 185)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 185)
    - 1982 (Box 185)
    - 1983 (Box 185)
    - 1984 (Box 185)
    - 1985 (Box 185)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 185)
  - National Medal of Science, 1971 (Box 185)
  - National Student Aid Coalition, 1982 (Box 185)
  - National Whale Symposium (Box 185)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 185)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 185)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1980 (Box 185)
  - New Harmony, Indiana, 1971-1979 (Box 185)
  - New University Conference (NUC) (Box 185)
    - 1968, (2 folders) (Box 185)
    - 1968-1969, (2 folders) (Box 185)
    - 1969, (8 folders) (Box 185)
    - 1970, (2 folders) (Box 185)
    - 1971, (2 folders) (Box 185)
  - New York (Box 185)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 186)
    - 1970-1982 (Box 186)
  - New York State University at Binghamton, 1978-1979 (Box 186)
  - State University of New York, 1980; (2 folders) (Box 186)
  - Newcomen Society (Box 186)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 186)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 186)
  - Newman Foundation (Box 186)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 186)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 186)
    - 1985 (Box 186)
    - 1987 (Box 186)
  - News Bureau (Box 186)
    - 1972 (Box 186)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 186)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 186)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 186)
    - 1975 (Box 186)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 186)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 186)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 186)
    - 1977 (Box 186)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 186)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 186)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 186)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 186)
    - 1983 (Box 186)
    - 1984 (Box 186)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 186)